this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this site can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
luffy was sent flying from the sabaody archipelago by bartholomew kuma after soaring through the sky
for hours he found himself in a kingdom inhabited entirely by women amazon living condemned as a
trespasser luffy is thrown into an arena and forced to battle to the death with the sisters of the snake
princess
i've never seen marigold salamander move before i can't wait
oh don't forget about sandersonia's eight-headed serpents
there not cracked are you
good just wait here okay real sorry you got turned into stone because of me
all done okay which one of you wants your ass kicked first what a joke
did he just say what i think he said if he thinks he can win he's in for an ugly surprise
hilarious let's find more men to feed to the gorgon sisters because this is too funny
marigold and sandersonia execute him now for the crime of sneaking onto our island and for
personally offending me bestow on him the ultimate punishment
what is it huh that was close
that hurt me but how
how is she doing that i can't get a punch in on her snake stick
damn it
what the hell are you doing you leave her alone
hey stop you're gonna end up breaking her
good idea
no stop
i said stop that's enough
the warriors are fainting
unreal that was the conqueror's spirit
you're kidding
i've never seen anyone besides our big sister do something like that
this boy has the qualities of a conqueror the ability to stand above all others
the same as me there's no doubt about it he wields such power but who the hell is this boy
is he toying with us
alright i get it now
you two girls are really strong back to the duel round two
all out special power battle
what are you hesitating for men are unworthy of our fear sisters
sonia
mary you can do it
What are you hesitating for?
Men are unworthy of our fear, sisters.
Sonia! Mary! You can do it!
Yeah! Teach that April lesson!
Ha! Rather silly to be so startled, right?
Indeed. If he can't control that hockey of his, then we have nothing to fear.
Okay, now.
If we're gonna go all out, we better move her out of the way.
Wouldn't want her to break.
Well, look at you making your little demands.
It seems you still don't understand the position you're in.
Perhaps smashing that statue will shut you up!
No, don't do it!
You should be fighting for your life. Why are you protecting that statue?
Because this was my fault.
And this is our fight! She has nothing to do with it!
Very well. Allow the man to move this statue.
But why?
I'd rather he stop his moaning and show us what he's truly capable of.
That way, when we grind him under our heels,
not only will he die a miserable laughingstock,
he'll finally understand how weak and useless men are.
All right.
Not that you're going anywhere, but hold on a little longer.
I'll figure something out after I beat up these big snake ladies.
Okay, now let's do this!
My, where does that confidence come from?
I don't know, but I shall enjoy beating it out of him.
You go ahead and try.
As long as you two stop yakking, it'll be worth it.
Insolent as ever, I see.
But you shall have your wish.
As long as I can dodge, I don't care if you spit that crap all day!
Now, gum gum!
Oh, what's up with this smoke?
I don't even have to hit you.
My poison can take many forms.
All deadly.
Marigold's poison gas attack is my favorite!
Maybe now I'll stop jumping around so much.
This stuff isn't so bad.
Oh, man.
I'm feeling kind of woozy.
You are my prey.
I'm done toying with you.
I'm killing you.
Slowly but surely.
I'll weaken you with poison.
I'll corner you.
And then finally, finish you.
You may have been speedy before,
but all it takes is one whiff of my poison
to dull your senses.
Damn it!
That's enough!
Now, gum gum gum!
Pants off!
And another one!
You're a mess.
Perhaps you'd like to lie down.
I laugh, but at this point, it's more of a tragedy.
No matter how strong they may be,
I can reduce any man to a whimpering weakling.
It's time to die!
The fight's over.
I'm not dizzy now!
What do you know?
The poison's all gone!
Phew!
Is that his hand?
Look, he's down there!
Persistent, isn't he?
Harry!
Sonia!
He's still alive!
Be careful!
That poison smoke's a pain in the ass!
I've got to come up with a plan!
All right, gum gum!
And fly away!
All that poison and smoke stuff was really getting on my nerves!
Now I can beat you guys up like I was supposed to!
He turned into a balloon and blew that poison away like it was nothing!
Can all men do that?
This is highly educational!
Is it, though?
So you're going to beat us up now, you said?
With as badly as you've been losing, I admit I have my doubts!
Just watch!
Okay, I'll show you what I can do when I go all out!
How are you?
Now second gear!
What's he doing now?
Is it me or is he steaming?
Men are kind of scary, aren't they?
They're nothing like us, that's for sure.
He's smoking!
This is incredible!
All out!
Do you mean to imply that you've been going easy on us?
He's blowing smoke figuratively and literally. Think nothing of it, sister.
Perhaps we've beaten the sense out of you and you've forgotten, but even if you're hot and steamy, we can still read your every move.
We'll see, won't we?
Come, come! Jet!
It's no use!
Pissed off!
You're not hurt, are you?
Whatever powers you possess, I assure you that ours are greater still.
In other words, boy, all your little trick has done is awaken our wrath.
Medusa here!
Eight-headed serpent!
We love you, Xander-sonia!
She bit through the fence!
Even though the snakes are just made out of her hair, those fangs hit as hard as iron!
Why can't I hit him?
I know what he's going to do, but somehow I still can't keep up!
What?
Oh!
payment
No!
Ah!
I don't want to import one.
Oh!
Ah!
Sonia, are you all right?
Come, come!
Don't bother.
As you've clearly seen before, your attacks simply bounce off of me.
As long as I can match your speed, you may strike as hard as you like, because my defenses shall not fail!
Let's find out.
Check!
My super!
Ah!
Sonia!
Mary!
If I recall, you were supposed to kill the man, not indulge in his foolish games.
But sister...
His transgressions are, in a word, unforgivable.
I refuse to tolerate him any longer.
Yes, of course we're very sorry, sister.
We'll finish him immediately.
Medusa hair!
Eight-headed servant!
Whoa!
She's on fire!
Medusa hair!
Salamander!
There's nowhere left to run, man!
If he doesn't get bitten, he's gonna get burned for sure!
Oh, this is my favorite attack!
There's nowhere left to run, man.
If he doesn't get bitten, he's gonna get burned for sure.
Oh, this is my favorite attack.
Now, come, come!
Check!
No, Sonya! I didn't mean to!
Hurry, get away from me!
Something is dragging me closer!
Our tail!
Not did he!
I'm burning!
It is burning!
Sonia, stop! You're pulling me!
Watch out, Sonya! Don't fall!
That's a pin of blades!
Hold on to the stands!
Whoa, that was close!
Andersonia, no!
No!
This is absolutely pathetic!
Her back is exposed!
Sonya!
You can't let our people see that!
He can't be!
I'm going to knock her down and skewer her!
Isn't winning enough, you animal!
Do you have to kick her while she's down too?
Are you here to mock me?
Don't move!
Even if you guys want to kill me,
that doesn't mean that I want to kill you!
Why of all the insolent?
Mary!
This is your chance to finish him off!
Don't just stand there!
Hurry!
I can't!
Don't you understand?
He isn't mocking you, sister!
That man is...
protecting us!
Oh no!
Sandersonia's clothing burned off in the fire!
Her back is showing!
If he gets off her, her gorgon eyes will be exposed!
Hurry and look away!
She's going to turn us all to stone!
I didn't even realize!
It's like your sister said before, right?
My secret is out.
He saw my back.
Then we mustn't let him leave the castle alive!
Why not?
What's the big deal?
I just saw her back!
What you saw is a secret we would die to protect.
Or rather, one that we would kill to protect in this particular instance.
You'd rather die than let people see this thing on your back, right?
Like I said, don't move!
This match is hereby over!
Everyone, you must leave the arena at once!
Do not gaze upon the gorgon eyes!
Try and pick her back up!
No!
Go!
Get out of here!
Get away!
a way!!
I've got her!
a way!
A 4-5-5-5-5-5-5-5-5-5-5-6-5-1-8-2-3-5-5-6-5-5-5-5-7-5-1-9-9-9-9-6-2-5-8-5-7-7-6-4-2-5-6-5-5-6-7-6-5-6-6-6-6-4-5!
You know that I was trying to kill you just a moment ago.
Why are you protecting me?
Because that mark on your back has nothing to do with our fight.
We can always settle things later.
You owe your lives to the man you tried to execute.
You must make a decision, but what will it be?
You may be able to fool this country,
but the time may come when you can no longer fool yourself, princess.
If you truly want to move forward in this world,
you must come to terms with what you wear on your back.
After Luffy protects the secret of the Snake Sisters, they decide to spare his life.
Hancock reveals the story behind the familiar mark on their backs.
The tale of her childhood is one of tragedy,
suffered at the hands of a corrupt group that Luffy knows all too well.
On the next One Piece, Hancock's Confession,
the Sisters Abhorrent Past,
I'm going to be king of the pirates!
this one of my allies,
the true parents.
The True Heroes Retreat,
the perfection!
this is not the hazy,
This is the one who is human nature documents,
the memory 들고 Haaple
and Mary Rose,
the chopstick is a measurement.
This is the one who is a weapon for
the bestinya.
You have no power,
theest in the captor.